我叫巴里·艾伦
My name is Barry Allen,
是现今世上速度最快的人
and I am the fastest man alive.
在外人看来
To the outside world,
我只是个普通的鉴证专员
I'm an ordinary forensic scientist.
但在尖端科研实验室的朋友们的帮助下
But secretly, with the help of my friends at S.T.A.R. Labs,
我秘密地打击犯罪  寻找跟我一样的超能力者
I fight crime and find other meta-humans like me.
但是我在时间中迷失了
But I became lost in time.
我的朋友们用尽了一切办法才把我救回来
It took everything in my friends' power to bring me back,
但我们的世界也因此出现了新的威胁
and in doing so our world was opened up to new threats.
我是唯一来得及阻止他们的人
And I'm the only one fast enough to stop them.
我是闪电侠
I am the Flash.
《闪电侠》前情回顾
Previously, on "The Flash"...
每个热点代表一个人体
Each of these heat scans indicates a human body.
12个标记  12个超能力者
12 markers, 12 metas.
他们找到目标的速度比我们想像得快
They identified the targets sooner than we planned.
也许吧
Perhaps.
方圆几公里都没有
There's nothing within miles of here
能产生暗物质的东西
capable of even creating dark matter.
三周前有
There was three weeks ago.
这是我从神速力出来的地方
This is where I came out of the Speed Force.
一波暗物质也和你一起冲出来了
And a wave of dark matter washed out with you.
你认为搞出武士机器人的幕后黑手
You think the guy behind the Samurai Robot--
机士
Samuroid.
他是想要我们造出一车超能力者
He wanted us to create a busload of metas?
我认为全都是有联系的
I think it's all connected.
你好啊  美女
Hello, gorgeous.
准备好呆笨了吗
You ready to get your schmoopy on?
乔  我怀孕了
Joe, I'm pregnant.
听我说  我在想
Look, I was thinking--
停  少想多亲
No, no. Less thinking, more kissing.
就等一下下
Okay, but hold on a minute.
我们之间  真的很好
This thing we got going on, this is real good.
还行
It's okay.
什么
What?
我开玩笑的  非常好
No, I'm just kidding. It's better than okay.
是的
Yeah, that's right.
非常好就对了
It's better than okay.
但是就是因为这个
But because of that,
我觉得我们的关系
I think we're at a place
已经到了时候
in our relationship
我该跟你说
where the guy says to his girl
那三个字了
those three magic words.
哪  哪三个字
What--what three words?
你叫啥
What's your name?
准确来说这是四个字
Well, that is technically four words.
其实就是三个字
Actually, technically it's three words
因为缩写只算一个字
'cause contractions are one word
而且语法就是这么规定的
and that's how grammar works.
不过这不是关键  你叫啥
That's not the point, though. What's your name?
吉普赛
Gypsy.
我叫吉普赛
My name is Gypsy.
真的吗  你出生后  有人就说
For real? So, you were born, and somebody was just like,
"以后你就叫吉普赛了"
"I'm gonna name you Gypsy?"
我就喜欢叫吉普赛
Gypsy is what I like to be called.
很神秘  还很忧郁
It is mysterious. And it's moody.
忧郁不错
Moody's right.
好吧
All right.
我要去洗手间了
I'm gonna go to the bathroom.
等我回来的时候
And when I get back,
你最好别再问我的名字了
you'd better stop asking me my real name.
还有把衣服脱下
And be wearing less clothes.
我并不需要知道你的名字
I don't need to know your name.
这个妹子  她要让你神魂颠倒*
*Mmm, this girl, she 'bout to rock your world
你死定了
You're a dead man.
那些可都是收藏品
Those are collectibles.
你是谁
Who are you?
老爸
Daddy?
很高兴见到你  先生
Pleased to meet you, sir.
他会把我放下吗
Is he gonna put me down?
闪 电 侠
第四季
第四集
可能你们有些人还不知道
You know, some of you may not realize,
我在当市长之前
but before I was mayor,
就在这间警局里当过警察
I was a cop in this very precinct.
正是有了这里的每位警员
And it's because of these men and women
中城的每家每户才能睡上安稳的觉
every family in Central City can sleep comfortably at night.
怎么回事
What's happening?
贝洛斯市长要竞选连任
Mayor Bellows is on his reelection campaign.
乔·韦斯特警探  工作一直那么优秀
Detective Joe West. Keep up the good work.
说两句吧  乔
What do you say, Joe?
就这样吧
I'll do that.
所以他成不了政治家
And that's why he's not a politician.
我烦他
I hate that.
是吗  想过跟他竞选吗
Yeah? Thought about running against him?
你能想像出你到处
Can't you picture yourself
跟人握手  亲小孩的画面吗
shaking hands and kissing babies?
什么
What?
没人说过还得亲小孩啊
Ain't nobody talking about babies.
你说你对巴士超能力者的事有线索了
You said you had a lead on this meta bus situation.
是的  跟我来
Yeah, I do. Come here.
支持贝洛斯
Fellow for Bellows!
\an8\pos(166.8,195.775)\fscx97\fscy135}拉姆齐·迪肯             贝琪·夏普
你把你母亲案子的照片都取下来了
You took the photos down from your mother's case.
是的  那个案子已经结了
Yeah, well, the case was solved.
这个案子还没有
This one isn't.
抓到了这两个  基尔戈和凶险星
We got these two. Kilgore and Hazard.
但是外面还有十个  在我从神速力
But that still leaves ten meta-humans that were created
回来时所创造的超能力者
when I came out of the Speed Force.
找十个坐公交车的乘客
How hard can it be to track
能有多难呢
down ten bus passengers?
根据交通部的数据
Well, according to the Department of Transportation,
那天有九百多个人坐过公交车
over 900 people rode that bus that day.
公交车司机呢
What about the bus driver?
说到这就更有趣了
That's where things get more interesting.
他死了
He's dead.
在自家的浴缸里淹死了
Drowned in his own bathtub.
一点都不可疑
That's not too suspicious.
哈里说这一切都有联系
Harry said it was all connected.
我觉得他是对的
I think he's right.
那个机士
I mean, the Samuroid
逼你们把我救回来
pushing you guys to bring me back,
我没从你们所想的地方出来
me not coming out of the place you thought I would,
大巴正好在那个地方
the bus being in the exact right place
被暗物质击中
to be hit by dark matter--
都是计划好的
It was planned.
没错  是某个聪明之人设计好的
Yeah. By somebody smart.
我们就很聪明
We're pretty smart.
我也觉得
Well, I think so.
我们再仔细查查大巴司机的死因
Okay, let's look closer into the bus driver's death.
也许会给我们一点线索
It may give us a lead.
我会让爱瑞丝从法医办公室
I'll have Iris pull up the autopsy report
调出尸检报告
from the coroner's office.
好的
Sounds good.
怎么
What?
我不知道
I don't know.
今早  你就像是
This morning, you're, like...
光彩照人
glowing.
什么光彩照人
What do you mean, "Glowing?"
我的意思是  你就像是有一股热情
I just mean, like, you got, like, a warmth about you.
就像是光效积木
Like a Lite-Brite.
没有热情  没有光彩照人
There's no warmth. No glow.
我也不是光效积木
And I ain't no damn Lite-Brite.
你在浪费时间  赶紧去尖端科研实验室
You're wasting time. S.T.A.R. Labs.
不仅光彩照人  还脾气暴躁
Glowing and irritable.
塞西尔怎么样了
How's Cecile?
很好  还是一样
Fine. The same.
我是说老样子
I mean, nothing's changed.
如果有什么变化  我会告诉你的
If something changes, I'll let you know.
好
All right.
这个地方都没人把守
This facility is poorly guarded.
显然是这样
Clearly.
别开火  牛仔
Okay. Power down, buckaroo.
好极了  你们俩都来了
Oh, good. You're both here.
西斯科  这是谁
Cisco, who is this?
这是穿越者
This is Breacher.
也是吉普赛的父亲
AKA Gypsy's father.
我看得出相像之处
Yeah, I, um, can see the resemblance.
我们没有相像之处
There is no resemblance.
你知道吉普赛在地球十九上
So, you know how Gypsy's kind of a big deal collectoron
是个了不起的回收者吧
on Earth-19?
她的上级就是就她爸爸
Well, her boss is her dad--
他决定在最适当的时间
who decided to pay us a little surprise visit
突然来造访我们
at the perfect time.
所以我决定带他来看看我工作的地方
Which is why I decided to show him around where I work.
-你懂的  -我叫巴里·艾伦
- You know? - I'm Barry Allen.
你是西斯科的私人助理
Cisco's personal assistant.
他的什么
His what?
他是我最好的私人助理
And he is the best personal assistant I've ever had.
他留得最晚  来得最早
He stays late, starts early.
总有一天  我会反过来替他打工的
One day, I'll be working for him.
你在干嘛
What are you doing?
我本来想给他留个好印象
I wanted to impress him,
现在我停不下来了
and now I can't stop.
我叫乔·韦斯特
Joe West.
执法人员
A fellow law man.
我敬重你
You, I can respect.
后面那位是哈里·威尔斯
And Harry Wells back there.
你长得很像我以前叫我女儿去追杀的一个人
You look like someone I once sent my daughter to kill.
很多人这么说
I get that a lot.
有谁能带他
Uh, I thought maybe someone would want to give him
到处转转吗
the, uh, the old look-see.
好主意  艾伦  韦斯特警探
Great idea. Um, Allen, Detective West,
不如你们带吉普赛的父亲
why don't you give Gypsy's father here
在实验室里四处转转
the nickel tour of the facilities?
乔
Joe.
三个小时了  我一直想去尿
I've had to pee for, like, three hours.
你搞什么
What is wrong with you?
你没看到他的表情吗
Have you seen his face?
那家伙杀人时也是这副表情
The guy's killed people with that face.
我可不是在说笑  吉普赛说那可是真事
I'm not even joking. Gypsy said that literally happened.
你想得到他的认同吧
You want his approval, right?
我是想得到他的认同  他是我女朋友的父亲
Yes, I want his approval. He's my girlfriend's father.
当然了  西斯科
Of course. Cisco, listen.
你是个优秀  正直
You're a fine, upstanding,
聪明又衣着整洁的年轻人
smart, well-groomed young man.
每个父亲都会很开心
Any father would be happy
看到你和他们的女儿交往
to have you date his daughter,
除了我
except me.
你不能和我女儿交往
Can't date my daughter, all right?
也不能和杰西交往  禁止和杰西交往
Can't date Jesse. Jesse's off limits.
你开口赞我
Went for the compliment,
却不攻自破
did not stick the landing.
带他去喝杯咖啡吧
Just take him for coffee, okay?
去喝杯咖啡  好好多了解他一点
Go for coffee, get to know him a little bit better.
我敢说你会感到很惊讶
I bet that you'll be pleasantly surprised
你们有很多的共同点
at how much you have in common, right?
你们都有同样的超能力  都是穿越者
You both have the same powers. You're breachers.
你的发型很奇葩
You have ridiculous hair.
他的发型也很奇葩
He has ridiculous hair.
好吧  但是
Okay, but--
而且你们俩都爱吉普赛
And you both love Gypsy.
你真的是在给我交往方面的建议吗
Are you actually giving me decent relationship advice right now?
没错
I am.
你会表现得很好的
You'll be fine.
我不想再待在这里了
I don't wanna be here anymore.
那我们要走了
And we're leaving.
救我
Help me.
一定要玩得开心
Have fun storming the castle.
为什么我见过最可怕的人
Why is the scariest person I've ever seen
徘徊在我们走廊里
roaming our halls?
因为西斯科
Cisco.
好吧  我拿到了
Okay, so, I've got the coroner's report
大巴司机的验尸报告
for the death of the bus driver,
但是似乎没有犯罪迹象
but it doesn't seem like there's any signs of foul play.
除此之外  只有他能告诉我们
Aside from him being the one guy that could have told us
大巴上还有些什么人
who else was on that bus.
他们登记了他的私人物品  看看有什么
They logged his personal effects, let's see...
信用卡  现金  收据
Credit cards, cash, receipts, um...
等等  上一张
Wait, go back.
拉尔夫·德比
私家侦探
我欠你五块车费
2017年10月10日
-拉尔夫·德比  -我完蛋了
- Ralph Dibny. - I'll be damned.
拉尔夫·德比是谁
Who is Ralph Dibny?
他曾经是个警察
He used to be a cop.
脏警  他被警队开除了
Dirty cop. He got kicked off the force.
因为什么
For what?
说来话长了
It's a long story.
就是他
That's him.
他挺帅的  就像是方下巴的
He's handsome in a square-jawed
奥利弗·奎恩一样
Oliver Queen kind of way.
你认真的
For real?
宝贝  你知道我眼里只有你
Babe, you know I've only got eyes for you.
欠条时间与我
The I.O.U. is dated the same day
从神速力中出来一样
that I came out of the Speed Force.
你觉得德比那天也在车上吗
You think Dibny was on the bus that day?
也许他现在是超能力者了
Maybe he's a meta-human now?
咱们去拜访他一下
Let's pay him a visit.
你看起来  有心事
You seem...something.
你和这个拉尔夫有什么故事吗
What's up with you and this Ralph guy?
就像乔说的  说来话长了
It's like Joe said. It's a long story.
奥利弗·奎恩很性感
Oliver Queen is hot.
阿门  哈利路亚
Amen, hallelujah.
我保证没有我破不掉的案子
I promised there wasn't a single case I couldn't crack.
拉尔夫·德比  私家侦探(混蛋)
而做下了保证就一定会完成
And a promise made is a promise kept.
德比查出了
Dibny detects.
你丈夫没有死在那飞机上  布鲁姆夫人
Your husband didn't die in that plane crash, Mrs. Broome.
他没有吗  那他在哪
He didn't? Then where is he?
接下来就是复杂的地方了
Well, that brings us to the difficult part.
原来他又结婚并搬到了明尼苏达
Turns out he got remarried and moved to Minnesota.
他现在有两个孩子  双胞胎
Has two kids now. Twins.
双子城的双胞胎
Twins in the twin cities.
别别别  别这样
No, no, no, no, no. Don't.
别为那个混蛋哭泣
Don't cry for that jerk.
他不配
He doesn't deserve it.
阳光依然明媚
The sun still shines.
小鸟依然吱喳而鸣
The birds, they still chirp.
吱吱  喳喳
Chirp, chirp.
布鲁姆夫人  你是位很有吸引力的女人
Mrs. Broome, you are a very attractive woman,
你肯定能找到其他人
and you will find someone else.
有一个人会抱着你
Someone who will hold you.
有一个人会抹去你的泪水
Someone who will wipe away those tears.
你喜欢吃虾吗
Do you like shrimp?
他绝对在这里了
This is definitely his place.
重新考虑过了
Reconsidered, huh?
-拉尔夫  -乔·韦斯特
- Ralph. - Joe West.
巴里·艾伦
Barry Allen.
好久不见了  菜鸟
Been a long time, rookie.
我已经不是菜鸟了  德比
Well, I'm not a rookie anymore, Dibny.
你看起来很健康
You look healthy.
对  把备用车胎
Yeah. Got the spare tire
从车里拿出来了  会有这种情况
out of the trunk. It happens.
也许有一天也会发生在你身上  瘦猴子
Might even happen to you, too, one day, Slim Jim.
那么  是什么让你们来到了德比之家
So what brings you boys to Casa de Dibny?
你四周前中午是不是在405路车上
Were you on the 405 bus four weeks ago around noon?
这个问题还真明确
That's a very specific question.
我们在一个死掉的公车司机物品里发现了
We found your I.O.U. From the deceased bus driver's
你的欠条
personal effects.
死了
Deceased? Hey.
我欠的人又少了一个
That's one less "U" I owe.
你俩想要什么
What's it to you two?
就是个简单的问题  你为什么不回答
It's a simple question. Why don't you just answer it?
你五年后走进我的办公室
You walk into my office after five years
好像什么都没发生过  还要我办事
like nothing ever happened, and ask me for a favor?
我问到了秘密
I smell a mystery.
不是要你办事  是要情报
It's not a favor. It's information.
那这情报值多少钱
And how much is this information worth?
你是要讹我们吗
Are you shaking us down?
我知道你不知道的情报
I know something you don't.
而你急需知道  不然的话你绝不会
And you need to know it badly, otherwise you'd never
在你做出那种事后  吞下自尊来找我
swallow your pride and face me after what you did.
我做的事
After what I did?
拉尔夫
Ralph.
那辆公车上的人暴露在了
The people on that bus were exposed
危险的物质之中
to a dangerous substance.
危险
Dangerous?
怎么个危险法  像是埃博拉病毒吗
Dangerous like what? Like...Ebola?
你在那辆车上吗
Were you on the bus?
不在
No.
好吧  咱们走
Okay. Let's go.
我听说你和一个性感的检察官搞上了
Hey, I heard you shacked up with that hot D.A.
她有姐妹吗
She got a sister?
好吧
Okay.
祝你好运  一路顺风
Good luck. All the best.
那么  你愿意出多少
So, what's it worth?
该死
Ah, crap.
伙计们  你们不想这样做的
Guys, you don't want to do this!
我不知道你想要什么
I don't know what you want.
咱们谈一谈怎样
Let's talk about this.
放我下来
Put me down.
别放我下去
Don't put me down!
那家伙真是一点都没变
That guy hasn't changed a bit.
你真以为他会变吗
You really expect him to?
我想他是在那辆车上
I guess he was on that bus.
伙计们  这是怎么回事
Hey, guys? What the hell?
是是  不用客气
Yeah, yeah, well, you're welcome.
我这是怎么了
What happened to me?
深呼吸  好吗
Breathe, okay?
-我在呼吸呢  -好
- I am breathing. - Okay.
显然这人是个公车超能力者
Clearly this guy is a bus meta.
这个有意思  暗物质将
This is interesting. The dark matter has
德比的细胞聚合了
polymerized Dibny's cells.
暗物质是什么鬼  为什么在我细胞里
What the hell is dark matter, and why is it in my cells?
你是说他体内所有的细胞壁
You're saying the walls of every cell
-都产生了弹性吗  -我是说它们在
- in his body have elasticized? - I'm saying they formed
原子级别形成了无法破坏的纽带
an unbreakable bond at the atomic level.
现在你可以拉伸那些细胞
Now you can stretch these cells
让那些细胞拉伸
and stretch these cells.
-就像弹性橡皮泥  -就像弹性橡皮泥
- Like Silly Putty. - Like Silly Putty.
我是弹性橡皮泥了
I'm Silly Putty?
不
No.
类似
Kinda.
我是弹性橡皮泥了
I'm Silly Putty?
拉尔夫
Ralph.
楼顶上的人是谁
Who were the guys on the roof?
那事现在还重要吗
Is that really the issue right now?
看看我
Look at me!
艾伦  你和你的尖端科研实验室怪咖
Allen, you and your S.T.A.R. Labs nerds
最好把我拼回去
better put me back together.
放手  我们在尽力帮你
Get your hands off me. We're trying to help you.
-你才没有  -闭嘴
- You're not trying to help me. - Shut up.
是不是  是不是
Come on! Oh, come on!
一会再说吧  我需要血液样本
You can do this later. I just need a sample of blood.
这是我的脸吗
Oh, is that my face?
四年来看到这种东西  我终于吐了
Four years seeing this stuff, I finally puked.
我能在那充电吗
Can I plug in?
老爸
Daddy.
我知道你爱我  我也爱你
I know you love me, and I love you.
我真的喜欢西斯科  我需要你俩处得来
I really like Cisco, and I need you two to get along.
你觉得你可以试一试吗
So do you think that you can try to do that?
为了你我什么都愿意做  宝贝
I'll do anything for you, petal.
3杯咖啡来啦
Ah, three coffees.
你呢
How about you, huh?
准备尝尝热爪哇咖啡吗
Ready for some hot java?
我所在的地球上没有咖啡
We don't have coffee on my Earth.
庄稼都被毁了
Crops were destroyed.
我所在的世界被多重宇宙中
My world was attacked-- invaded--by the worst,
最邪恶的生物攻击...侵略了
most evil creatures in the multiverse.
我就再也不喝咖啡了
I'll never drink coffee again.
-我喝两杯  -没事的
- Two for me. - It's okay.
老爸  我给你点杯茶吧
Daddy, why don't I get you a tea?
养心茶那种吗
Like a relaxing tea?
-对  -去点吧
- Yeah. - Please.
-好的  -辛苦了
- Okay. - Thanks.
坐下了
Pop a squat. Uh...
我知道站在朋友同时也是父亲的角度上
I know from a friend-- who is also a father--
女儿对他有多重要
how important his daughter is to him.
我也想让您知道您的女儿
And I just wanted to let you know how important
对我来说有多重要
your daughter is to me.
在我们彼此了解多一些之后
And that after you and I get to know each other a little,
也许我们能发现...
maybe we might find that...
我们并没有那么不同
we're not so different.
我会狩猎你
I'm going to hunt you.
你配不上她
You're not worthy of her.
这不是应该由她来决定吗
Isn't that for her to decide?
Ten.
而且  我发誓听到你说
Also, I could have sworn you said,
你要对我进行狩猎
uh, you were gonna hunt me.
是像猎杀小鹿一样吗
What, like a deer?
我猎杀过历史上最坏的
I have hunted some of the worst
缺口罪犯
breach criminals in history.
黑暗之王玛拉  希德拉的苏鲁加
Marla the Dark Lord. Soolunga of Sheerdra.
斯凯的沙人
The Sand People of Scar.
你对于我而言太简单了
You will be easy prey.
Nine.
我尽量对您很礼貌了
Listen, I have tried to be polite with you,
但这有点太过了
but this is going a little too far.
我知道你保护欲很强
I get that you're overprotective--
Eight.
-你是在倒数吗  -在这24小时之内
- Are you counting? - For the next 24 hours,
我会在整座城市猎杀你
I will be hunting you throughout this city.
我们都不能使用各自的超能力
We will not use our powers.
但一切结束后
But when it's over,
我女儿就和你再无关系了
my daughter will be free of you.
Seven.
你对她历任男朋友都这样吗
Do you do this with all her boyfriends?
我也猎杀了上一个  是的
I hunted her last one, yes.
他现在人呢
Where is he now?
不知道
I don't know.
-他逃跑了  -我不知道
- He got away. - I don't know
人死了之后会去哪里
where you go when you die.
Five.
你跳过了6
You just skipped six.
我知道  4
I know. Four.
别试着打开缺口逃跑
And don't try to breach.
你这么做我会知道的
I'll know it if you do.
你躲不出我手掌心的  我要是你
You can't hide from me. So if I were you,
我会开始跑的 西斯斯
I would start running, Cisky.
3  2  1
Three, two, one.
该死
Damn.
他开始狩猎了
He's hunting him.
终于让他冷静下来了
I finally calmed him down.
一个人处于溶胶状态时
Amazing what 50 milligrams of Lorazepam can do
50毫克安定剂的作用可真神奇
when you get it in aerosol form.
有什么办法把他拼回去吗
Is there anything you can do to put him back together?
拜托  我的胃扛不住了
Please, my stomach can't take much more.
我想我能稳定他的细胞  但是我需要
I think I could stabilize his cells if I had a sample
他在巴士上
of his DNA from prior to when
接触暗物质之前的DNA样本
he was exposed to the dark matter on the bus.
为什么 那样他就可以
Why? So he can go out
开始出去伤害别人
and start hurting people,
和他其他那些朋友一样
like our other friends here?
我觉得应该把他关在管道监狱
I think we should lock him up in the Pipeline.
他什么也没做
He hasn't done anything.
是还没做  相信我
Yet. Trust me.
我知道他  是个坏家伙
I know this guy. He's a bad guy.
巴里  我曾宣誓要帮助别人
Barry, I took an oath to help people.
我是个医生  我不能把他
I'm a doctor. I can't just leave him
像意大利面一样丢在那里
in there like spaghetti.
恶人
Villains?
对
Yeah.
那辆巴士上的人如今都比从前
Every person that was on that bus is now 1,000 times
凶险1000倍
more dangerous than they were before.
包括德比
Dibny included.
-如果他变了呢  -本性难移
- What if he's changed? - People don't change.
我就变好了
I did.
我变成冰霜杀手时
When I became Killer Frost,
你仍然相信我
you still believed in me.
你是好人  他...
You're a good person. He's...
不是
not.
巴里  我们回去德比的办公室怎么样
Barry, how about you and I go back to Dibny's office?
给凯特琳找一份DNA样本
Find a DNA sample for Caitlin?
老爸  你回中城警局  看看能从
Dad, you go back to CCPD, see what you can
德比身上查到些什么
dig up on Dibny?
好的  老大
Yes, boss.
看起来有人来这搜过了
Looks like someone tossed this place.
对  可能是把德比
Yeah. Probably the same guys
倒挂在屋顶的那帮人
that hung Dibny off the roof.
你为什么这么想
Why do you think?
我不知道  像他那样的人很可能
I dunno. Guy like that probably has
有一堆人想把他从屋顶上扔下去
a long list of people that wanna toss him off rooftops.
那你为什么想呢
Why do you want to?
-没  真的  -你俩
- No, seriously. - What happened between
之间怎么了
the two of you?
那是我做初级犯罪现场鉴证员的第一个案子
It was one of my first cases when I was a junior CSI.
德比是案子的负责人
Dibny was the lead detective.
什么案子
What case?
一位名叫朱迪·吉姆林的女子被刺死了
A woman named Judy Gimlin was stabbed to death.
她的丈夫里根是头号嫌疑人
Her husband, Reagan, was the prime suspect.
但没有证据  没有能把他
But there was no evidence-- nothing to tie him
和犯罪现场联系在一起的东西
to the crime scene.
然后  德比奇迹般地发现了一把刀
And then, Dibny miraculously found a knife
上面有丈夫的指纹
with the husband's fingerprints.
案子结了  德比成了英雄
Case closed. Dibny was a hero.
我不知道  可能因为我妈也被刺伤
I don't know, maybe because my mom was stabbed,
我想确定一下  于是我分析了那把刀
I wanted to be sure. So I analyzed the knife.
刀刃的锯齿和
The serrations on the blade did not match
受害者的伤口并不吻合
the wound on the vic.
所以是德比栽赃的
So Dibny planted the knife.
没错  然后他还撒谎了
Yep. And then he lied about it.
在誓言之下
Under oath.
-你揭露他了吗  -他不仅
- And you busted him? - I mean, he didn't just
打破了规则  他还犯了伪证罪
bend the rules, Iris. He committed perjury--
篡改了证据  他违背了警察职责
evidence tampering. He was thrown off the force.
重点是  他之前就不是好人
Point is, he was crooked then.
现在也不是
He's crooked now.
你觉得凯特琳需要多少DNA
Hey, how much DNA do you think Caitlin needs?
不用太多
Not much.
好的
Okay.
你觉得这个行不
Oh, think this will work?
巴里
Barry!
我猜有人比你更恨他
I guess someone hates him more than you do.
那就是通过震动穿越物体的感觉
And that's what it feels like to vibrate through solid matter.
你俩没受伤真是太好了
I'm just glad you two weren't hurt.
还不是因为你那位新朋友
No thanks to your new buddy in there.
他不是我的新朋友  他是我的患者
He's not my buddy. He's my patient.
凯特琳  我就不懂了
Caitlin, I just don't understand
你为什么要维护他
why you're defending him.
因为我了解那种感觉
Because I know what it's like
突然发现自己
to suddenly find yourself
有了强大的能力
with extraordinary powers
并且完全被吓到
and be totally freaked out by it.
就此而言  你也是
And so do you, for that matter.
你和我都曾在这个实验室中醒来
You and I both woke up in this lab once knowing that our lives
知道我们的生活再也不同了
would never be the same.
所以对那家伙有点同情心  好吧
So how about you give the guy a little sympathy?
各位
Guys.
我通过资料查询系统查了德比的电话
I pulled the LUDS on Dibny's phone.
他给市长办公室
There were 15 phone calls
打了15通电话
between him and the Mayor's office.
贝洛斯市长和拉尔夫·德比有什么事
What is Mayor Bellows doing talking to Ralph Dibny?
看啊  是我的好哥们巴里·艾伦
Oh, look. It's my good buddy Barry Allen.
有人刚炸了你的办公室
Someone just blew up your office.
太好了  可以保险索赔了
Sweet. Insurance claim.
我未婚妻和我差点死了
My fiancee and I almost died.
你搞定了韦斯特的女儿
You landed West's daughter?
艾伦可真是顺风顺水啊
Everything's coming up Allen.
好工作  女朋友
The job. The girl.
谁想杀你  德比
Who's trying to kill you, Dibny?
你知道在过去的五年
Do you know how many people I have pissed off
我惹毛了多少人吗
in the last five years?
愤怒的丈夫  愤怒的妻子
Angry husbands. Angry wives.
给出轨的配偶拍照
Not exactly dealing with high society
可不是什么上层社会的活
taking photos of cheating spouses.
那你为什么要和市长打电话
Then why are you talking to the Mayor?
谁说我打了
Who says I am?
你的电话记录
Your phone records.
你申请搜查令了吗
Did--did you get a warrant for that?
因为我知道你可是按规则办事的
'Cause I know you're all by-the-book.
你和贝洛斯市长到底有什么事
What's your business with Mayor Bellows?
没事  就打电话告诉他
Nothing. Just calling to tell him
我觉得他的工作成果显著
what a swell job I think he's doing.
说了15次
15 times?
12次都是误拨
12 of those were butt dials.
好吧  随便
All right, look, whatever.
我们可以自己去见市长
Maybe we'll go talk to the Mayor ourselves.
他可是乔的铁粉
You know, he's a huge fan of Joe's.
行  你去吧
Yeah, you go do that.
好的
All right.
我就待在这儿
I'm gonna stay here.
伸伸腿
Stretch my legs.
拉蒙  你觉得这明智吗
Ramon, do you think it's wise to be sneaking around
在技术武器装备周边乱跑
a technologically weaponized facility?
比我在外面面临的可安全多了
It's a lot safer than what I'm up against out there, so--
看来  咖啡喝得不怎么样
Coffee didn't go well, I take it?
吉普赛的爸爸要追猎我24个小时
Well, Gypsy's dad wants to hunt me for 24 hours
看看我是否配得上他女儿
to see if I'm worthy of his daughter--
不能使用超能力  根本不知道
no powers--so, don't know what the hell
我应该怎么办
I'm supposed to do about that.
反击啊
Fight back.
说真的  你好像在听一样
I swear, it's like you're trying to listen,
但你只是在想其他事的同时点点头
but you just nod while you're thinking of something else.
你现在就在这么做
You're doing it right now.
反击
Fight back.
拉蒙  你说什么
Ramon, what did you say?
你说不能用超能力
You said no powers?
对  继续
Yeah, go ahead.
除了震波外
Well, in addition to being Vibe,
你还有其他超能力  你脑子聪明
you have another superpower-- you're smart in here.
表面上看  你很弱
All right? Outwardly, you're weak.
太过了
All right? Too much.
但用你表面的弱
But use your outwardly weak appearance
作为你的优势  他预测的是
to your advantage. He's gonna anticipate
一个可悲的目标  你确实很可悲
a pathetic target. Well, you're pathetic.
你很可悲  你很弱
You're pathetic. You're weak.
一点帮助没有  只有伤人
Not helping, just hurting.
我的意思是  设个陷阱
All I'm saying is, set a trap, okay?
在他的游戏中战胜他  设个陷阱
Beat him at his own game. Set a trap.
-设个陷阱  -没错  陷阱
- Set a trap. - That's right, a trap.
陷阱  我能做到
A trap, I can do.
如果他是猛兽
'Cause he may be the Predator,
我就是施瓦辛格
but I'm the Schwarzenegger.
他在哪儿
Where is he?
他刚才还在
He was here.
他往那边走了
He went that way.
我放了个屁
I farted.
还不知道我下面
I'm not sure everything's still
变成了什么样
where it's supposed to be down there.
把这个喝了
Drink this.
这是什么
What is it?
我不会轻易就喝
I don't just drink stuff.
我的身体很金贵
My body is a temple.
知道  喝掉
Clearly. Drink it.
我只想知道是什么
I wanna know what it is.
百分之十七的酒精
It's 17% alcohol.
应该早说重点  亲爱的
You should have lead with that, sister.
到底是什么
What was that?
血清硫  氧化锌和硬脂酸
It's a serum of sulfur, zinc oxide, and steric acid
能交联你的聚合细胞
to cross-link your polymerized cells.
说人话
In English.
能治好你
It's gonna fix you.
成功了  我痊愈了
You did it. I'm cured.
不算痊愈  我只是用一种稳定的酶
Well, not cured. All I did was introduce
通过硫化反应
a stabilizing enzyme to reset your body
将你的身体重设为默认形状
to default shape through vulcanization.
像是肌肉记忆
It's like muscle memory.
肌肉记忆吗
Muscle memory, huh?
多久前的记忆
How far back memory, you think?
不确定
I don't know.
你想回到什么时候
Think about the shape you want to be
就能回到什么时候
and just be it.
我恢复了  就像海姆斯沃斯一样
I'm back. I look like a Hemsworth.
雷神扮演者
约瑟夫
Joseph.
谢谢您能来将我们
Thank you for meeting us.
刚好路过然后去一家医院剪彩
Quick stop on my way to a hospital ribbon cutting.
没关系的
No problem.
你怎么了  容光焕发啊
What's with you? You're glowing.
-我没  -你有
- N-no, I'm not. - You are.
有什么需要我帮忙的吗
Well, how can I help you, gentlemen?
今天还有很多事要做
I've got a lot on my schedule today.
我们不会占用您太多时间  市长先生
Ah, we won't take up much of your time, Mr. Mayor.
您认识拉尔夫·德比吗
Do you know a man named Ralph Dibny?
没想起来  他是谁
Doesn't ring a bell. Who is he?
之前是一名警察后来变成了私人侦探
Well, he's a former cop turned private investigator.
-应该不认识  -真的吗
- I don't think so. - Really?
他给您的办公室打了十几通电话
He called your office over a dozen times.
我得去问问秘书
Oh, I'm gonna have to check with my secretary.
安东尼  你以前也是警察
Anthony, you used to be a cop.
现在不是我们和市长之间谈话
We're not talking to the mayor, here.
是三个警察的谈话
It's three cops talking.
警察之间的话
Whatever cops say to each other,
只会有警察知道
they don't say to anybody else.
你和德比之间发生了什么
What's going on with you and Dibny?
我...
I...
-犯了错  -错
- made a mistake. - A mistake?
犯错是指
You mean like the kind of mistake you make
婚外情吗
with a woman who's not your wife?
只有那一次  乔
It was only that one time, Joe.
那一刻我就后悔了
I regretted it the moment I did it,
然后我们就分手了
and I broke it off right away.
后来德比出现了  他有我们的照片
And then Dibny shows up, and he's got pictures of us.
他威胁我说  不交赎金就发给我妻子
And he threatens to show them to my wife unless I pay him.
-多少钱  -很多
- How much? - Not enough.
那些电话
All those phone calls,
就是想敲诈更多的钱
it was him negotiating for a bigger price.
我爱我的家人  乔
I love my family, Joe.
让我把钱付给他
Just let me pay him,
这件事情就完结了
and I'll be done with it.
不市长先生  不必如此
No, Mr. Mayor, you're not gonna have to do that.
我们会处理的
We're gonna take care of it.
乔  巴里  谢谢你们
Joe, Barry. Thank you.
德比还真是变了不少
So much for Dibny changing.
德比还活着
Dibny's alive and talking.
找到他  我要看到照片和他的人头
Find him. I want those pictures and his head.
那些警察呢
And the cops?
我会在乎警察吗
What do I care about cops?
一同做掉
Waste 'em.
你的体征相当棒
Your vitals are fantastic.
没错
Yeah.
你勒索了市长吗
You're blackmailing the Mayor?
果然是巴里·艾伦  真是开门见山
Classic Barry Allen. Enters room and accuses wildly.
我们知道照片的事  拉尔夫
We know about the photos, Ralph.
贝洛斯都告诉我们了
Bellows told us everything.
又不是我让他出轨的
I'm not the one who told him to step out on his wife.
这就是你的辩解吗
That's your defense?
利用他的错误来敲诈
It's his fault that you're extorting him?
你说起来是不是很轻松
Isn't that a little easy for you to say?
你有梦幻的实验室  稳定的工作
Your fancy lab, your good job,
性感的女朋友
and your hot girlfriend?
可是像我这样的人
People like me are just trying to get
只能不断地还账单
from one bill to the next.
如果不是你夺走了我的工作
And I wouldn't have to be living like that
我也不会过得这么惨
if you hadn't cost me my job.
你是咎由自取
You got yourself fired.
你篡改了证据  陷害了那个人
You tampered with evidence. You framed that guy.
他罪有应得
Because he was guilty.
他逃脱了谋杀妻子的罪名
And he was gonna get away with killing his wife,
是你把他放走了
and then you let him go.
我是一名优秀的警察  优秀的侦探
I was a good cop. I was a good detective.
我失去了一切
I lost everything.
市长有很多钱
Mayor's got plenty of money.
他付得起这些钱
He can afford to spare a little.
就当是你给我的退休金吧
Consider it the pension you cost me.
善良的人不会把害人当做高尚
Good people don't destroy lives and call it noble.
你以前卑劣  现在也卑劣
You were dirty then. You're dirty now.
永远都会这样
Live with that.
你别想离开
You're not going anywhere.
放开我
Get off me.
你在逗我玩吗
Are you kidding me?
谢谢你毁了我的人生两次  艾伦
Thanks for ruining my life twice, Allen.
西斯科
Cisky.
出来吧
Show yourself.
没人能躲我一辈子
No one can avoid me forever.
我没打算躲
I'm not going to.
你在逗我玩吗
Are you kidding me?
道别吧  我的小敌人
Say good-bye, my little enemy.
搞什么鬼
What the Sheol?
瞧谁有全息图
Guess who's got a hologram?
你一定在想这是什么
Bet you're wondering what this is.
这是有振荡电力网的
This is an anti-vibrational force field
反振动力场
with an oscillating power grid.
对逆闪电挺合适的
It's good enough for the Reverse-Flash,
对你也挺合适的
good enough for you.
你最好举白旗投降
So you might as well wave your white flag,
因为你无法离开这玩意
'cause you aren't getting out of this thing
直到钟声敲响西斯科的胜利
until the clock strikes Cisco's victory.
胜利的感觉很好
Oh, victory. Feels good.
我从地球48的猎杀者
I pulled this from the body
身上拔出这个
of an Earth-48 hunter-killer.
你不能诱捕诱捕者
You can't trap a trapper.
我只是需要冷静一下
I just needed to cool off.
我知道
I figured.
德比好像让你挺心烦的
Dibny seemed to have gotten under your skin.
你为什么这么在意他当坏人呢
Why is it so important to you that he be the bad guy?
我在中城警局开始上班时
When I first started at CCPD,
我只在意规则
all I cared about was the rules.
但过去这几年
But, you know, these last few years,
我们没有经过审讯就把超能力者关起来
we've locked up meta-humans without a trial.
玩转时间与空间  搅和其他的世界
Played with time and space, messed with other worlds.
是的  但这跟德比有什么关系
Yeah, but what does that have to do with Dibny?
我们做的所有事
Just that everything that we've done we did
都是为了帮人
because we were trying to help people.
保护他们的安全
Keep them safe.
那时德比不也是在做这个吗
Is that all Dibny was trying to do back then?
好人不会杀人  然后觉得高尚
Good people don't destroy lives and call it noble.
那时我没犯错误吗
Did I make a mistake back then?
我没有害死好人吗
Did I cost a good man his life?
我不知道  巴仔
I don't know, Bare.
他违法和越过界限了
He did break the law-- cross the line.
但你没让他那么做
But you didn't make him do that.
你没有让他勒索市长
And you didn't make him blackmail the Mayor.
但也许凯特琳是对的
But, maybe Caitlin was right.
任何人经历你和她经历过的
Everyone who's gone through what you and her
现在德比在经历
and now Dibny's gone through--
也许应该给他第二次机会
maybe he deserves a second chance.
我来开
I got it.
艾伦  韦斯特警探
Allen. Detective West.
你俩不是市长的安保人员吗
Aren't you two on the Mayor's detail?
抱歉来你家打扰你了  调度刚才广播了
Sorry to bother you at home, but dispatch just radioed.
辛格队长要你马上去局里
Captain Singh needs you down at station ASAP.
好吧  让我去拿我的外套
All right, let me get my jacket.
巴仔
Bare!
总是干不腻
That never gets old.
那两人是市长的人
Those two work for the Mayor.
他们刚想杀了我们
They just tried to kill us.
德比是下一个
Dibny's next.
西斯斯  西斯斯  西斯斯
Cisky, Cisky, Cisky.
西斯斯
Cisky.
出来  出来受死吧
Come out. Come out and meet your end.
塑胶机器人
Plastoid.
你的物种毁了我的星球
You creatures destroyed my planet.
现在我要把你们全部杀掉
Now I will kill every last one of you.
各位  谁在那里
Guys, anyone there?
巴里  我在这里  是我
Barry, I'm here. It's me.
怎么了
What's up?
我要你激活我在德比身上
I need you to activate
放的追踪器
the tracker I put on Dibny.
你在拉尔夫身上放了追踪器
You put a tracker on Ralph?
塑胶机器人
Plastoid.
西斯科  你知道他在哪里吗
Cisco, do you know where he is?
他在市政厅
He's at City Hall.
你变瘦了
You lost weight.
胃束带手术
Lap band surgery.
既然没法杀死你
Since killing you didn't work out,
我就给你我们商定的二十万
what we agreed upon. 200K.
把照片给我
Let me have the photographs.
照片都在这里
Here's the pictures.
-钱你留着吧  -什么
- Keep the money. - What?
-我收回  -收回什么
- I take it back. - Take it back?
收回我的勒索
I take my blackmail back.
-你是在耍花样吗  -我不贪
- Is this some kind of a trick? - I'm not dirty.
我不想再搅和这种事了
And I don't want any part of this anymore.
而且别忘了  你让你的人在我办公室放炸弹
And don't you forget, I can tie you to that bomb
这件事我有证据
you had your goons plant in my office,
所以如果你不走开  我就去报警
so if you don't walk away, I will go to the cops.
-那还是勒索  -不  不是
- That's still blackmail. - No, it's not.
根本就是  你在告诉我如果我
Yes, it is. You're telling me if I don't
不给你这笔钱  你就不会报警
give you this money, you won't go to the cops.
好吧  我在勒索你
Okay, fine. I am blackmailing you
不要被勒索
into not being blackmailed.
所以  我们没事了
So, we're good, then.
是的  我们没事了
Yeah, we're good.
子弹鼻屎  超级恶心
Bullet booger. Super gross.
抱歉  市长先生  结束了
Sorry, Mr. Mayor. It's over.
受死吧  塑胶机器人
Die, Plastoid, die!
你不能像扰乱我的世界那样
You will not infest this world
扰乱这个世界  塑胶机器人
as you did mine, Plastoid.
塑胶机器人  他在说我吗
Plastoid, what? Is he talking to me?
穿越者  站住
Breacher, stop.
-好吧  -他死定了  极速者
- Okay. - He dies, speedster.
进去  乔  你跟我来
Get in there, Joe. You're coming with me.
闪电侠
Flash!
你不必这么做
Look, you don't have to do this.
不  我需要
Yes, I do.
放过他
Leave him alone.
他没有侵略你的星球
This guy didn't invade your planet.
他没做任何错事
He didn't do anything wrong.
他变成这样是因为我和我的团队
He's like this 'cause of me and my team.
如果你对他和他的超能力不满
So if you've got a problem with him and his powers,
就找我处理
then you deal with me.
没事了吧  因为我必须
Hey, are we good here? Because I definitely
换我的内裤
gotta change my drawers.
市长带走了乔
The Mayor took Joe.
我现在跑得不够快
I can't run fast enough right now.
我的速度无法从大楼跳下
I'll never have enough speed to jump off a building.
你能打开缺口让我上去吗
Can you breach me up there?
不行  直升机
No way. The event horizon would rip
会被视界撕裂
that helicopter apart.
但我们得救乔
But we've gotta save Joe.
我们该怎么做
What do we do?
你可以上去
You can get me up there.
-我吗  -是的
- Me? - Yeah.
-怎么做  -你可以伸展
- How? - You can stretch.
抓住它
Grab it.
你疯了吗  我做不到
Are you--are you crazy? I can't do that.
不  你能做到  好吗
Yes, you can. All right?
我知道你的内心
I know that you have it inside you
是想帮助其他人的
to help someone other than yourself.
我了解你  拉尔夫
I know you, Ralph.
你怎么可能了解我
How could you possibly know me?
老兄  你在逗我玩吗
Dude, are you kidding me?
你就是闪电侠
You're the Flash?
其他人被闪电击中死掉
Everyone else gets struck by lightning and dies,
-而你获得了超能力  -拉尔夫  没错
- and you get super powers? - Ralph, yeah, that's right.
你的助手是个极速者
Your assistant's a speedster?
我喜欢闪电侠  但我现在得恨闪电侠了
I liked the Flash. Now I have to hate the Flash.
拉尔夫  保持专注  我现在需要你这么做
Ralph, focus. I need you to do this.
乔需要你这么做  拜托了
Joe needs you to do this. Please.
向我展示我看错你了  你说你曾是个好警察
Show me I was wrong about you. You said you were a good cop.
现在就当好警察吧
Be one right now.
搞什么鬼
What the hell?
我抓住了
I got it!
-帮帮忙  -坚持住  拉尔夫
- Help! - Hold on, Ralph.
塞西尔怀孕了
Cecile's pregnant.
我们到达终点了
Well, we've reached the end of our road.
虽然我们在路上跌跌撞撞过
We had some stumbles along the way,
但我们振作起来  我们回到家了
but we pulled it together. We made it home.
我恨你
I hate you.
还以为那能行呢
Really thought that one would work.
但我尊重你
But I respect you.
你是个坚定的战士
You're a steadfast warrior
与最凶恶的敌人战斗  保护你的朋友和
who would fight the fiercest of enemies to protect your friend
我唯一爱的人
and the only person I love.
至死方休  先生
With my dying breath, sir.
我知道  但我还是恨你
I know that, but I still hate you.
我从来没看见他那样夸赞人
I have never seen him gush like that.
那是夸赞吗
That's gushing?
他对我的爱让我受宠若惊
I'm terrified to experience him loving me.
好吧  那是我的工作
Well, that's my job.
没错  确实是
Oh, that's right. It is.
我感觉正在出现17号缺口
I feel a code-17 breach in progress.
我们现在得走了  辛西娅
We have to leave now, Cynthia.
辛西娅
Cyn-Cynthia?
辛西娅  你父亲叫什么
Cynthia. What's your dad's name?
乔希
Josh.
辛西娅和乔希  很好
Cynthia and Josh. That's great.
现在没那么惊吓了  辛西娅
Not so scary now, Cynthia.
继续那么叫试试
Keep calling me that. See what happens.
好吧
All right.
再见  吉普赛女郎
See you around...Gypsy.
-我修好你的办公室了  -天啊
- I fixed up your office. - Sweet fancy Moses.
谢谢你搞砸了我的保险索偿
Thanks for screwing up my insurance claim.
没有赔偿金  没有市长的钱
No payout, no mayor money.
我得马上搞个案子
I gotta pick up a case soon.
如果我给你个工作呢
What if I had a job for you?
我现在想大笑
I wanna laugh really hard right now,
但我怕我的脸会再掉下来
but I'm afraid my face will fall off again.
我无法改变
I can't change what has happened
我们之间的过去
between us in the past,
但我能给你机会改变
but I can offer you a chance to change what happens
-我们的未来  -怎么做
- in our future. - How?
让我和我的团队研究你的超能力
Let my team and I study your powers,
找出改进的办法  找出你的极限
figure out how to improve them, see what your limitations are.
让我训练你
And let me train you.
训练我做什么
Train me? For what?
做我做的事
To do what I do.
再当警探  拉尔夫
To be a detective again, Ralph.
真正的  但不会很轻松
A real one. Like, it's not gonna be easy.
我会把你逼到极限
I'm gonna push you to your limit.
可以肯定地说你有一天会恨我
I think it's safe to say some days you're gonna hate me.
艾伦  可以肯定地说我一直很恨你
Allen, it's safe to say that I always hate you.
我有很酷的超级英雄名吗
Do I get a cool super hero name?
你觉得塑胶人怎么样
What do you think about... Plastic Man?
我觉得那是我听过最蠢的名字
I think that's the dumbest name I've ever heard of.
西斯科负责取名字
Yeah, Cisco comes up with the names.
最好是那样
It's better that way.
你觉得怎么样
What do you say?
我要问你件事
There's just one thing I gotta ask you.
你当初为什么调查贝洛斯市长
What made you look into Mayor Bellows in the first place?
是个客户  让我跟着市长
Oh, it was a client. Asked me to follow the Mayor.
但我没见过他
Never met him, though.
都是通过电话联络
He did everything over the phone.
他是谁
Who was it?
只知道他的姓
Only gave me his last name.
迪沃
DeVoe.
我和你为敌已经很多年
You and I have been enemies for years.
当然你还有别的敌人
Oh, you've had others, of course.
有斯旺  极速和迪沃
There's Thawne. Zoom. DeVoe.
我们就是在这里想到用来对付
This is where we came up with the cerebral inhibitor
迪沃的大脑抑制剂
to use against DeVoe.
怎么了
What's wrong?
迪沃这个名字对你有什么意义吗
The name DeVoe mean something to you?
我察觉到了神秘
I smell a mystery.